Are you doing something like an idiot?
何かおばかさんとかやってるやつ?
I played Badament when I was in middle school.
中学の時にバダメントやってました
Even now?
今 も?
Because I'm doing it individually.
個人でやってるところだから
I guess it's pretty loose.
結構ゆるいんだろうな
Will you not be messed with?
いじられたりしない?
There may be many strange old men.
変なおじさんは多いかもしれない
It's like Darugarami.
だるがらみみたいな
But there are times when I am asked.
でも聞かれた時はある
That's not true.
それはないですね
OF.
NG
OF?
NG?
OF.
NG
Do you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いるの?
I'm not there.
いないです
Is it fun to be alone?
一人で楽しい?
What do you do on your day off?
休みとか何してる?
I sleep during my days off.
休みは寝てます
Would you like to go out?
遊びに行かない?
But I go out with friends, but even when I don't really have anything to do, I just sleep.
でも友達と遊びには行くけど、本当に用事がない時もひたすら寝て
Masu.
ます
Would you like to go on a date?
デ ートとかしないですか?
Well, I guess I should take some time alone.
まあ、一人の時間しないかな
Everyone was having fun and having fun together,
あんまりみんなでワイワイとか遊びたりとか、
Don't you like that?
そういうの好きじゃない?
No, I like it.
いや、好きですよ
It's important in that sense.
そういう意味に大事
Like.
みたいな
Why are you staying up late?
何で夜更かししてるの?
I'm staying up late.
夜更かししてます
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I'm watching YouTube.
YouTube見てます
Does anyone have YouTube?
YouTubeはいるやつ?
Tokai On Air.
東海オンエアとか
for example?
例えば?
Interesting for now.
とりあえず面白い
Planning ability.
企画力とか
企画力
Is it interesting?
面白いかな
I guess it's Johnny's or something.
ジャニーズとかですかね
There is.
ありますよ
Like an official channel?
公式チャンネルみたいな?
It's a secret.
秘密です
Hoshigai Chuo?
星街中央とか?
there is.
あります
What are you doing?
何してる?
Yeah.
うん
Can I put a pillar too?
柱も置いていいですか?
Where do your friends study?
友達はどこで学体するんですか?
How long do you wake up?
どれくらいで起きてるんですか?
How much?
誰くらいで?
Yeah.
うん
How long should I wear the shoes?
いつくらいくつくらいから
About a second year high school student.
高校2年生ぐらい
Are you coming suddenly?
急に来るの?
I don't know.
わかんない
I noticed.
気づいたな
Like.
みたいな
Yes, something like that.
はい、 みたいな
Aren't you horny?
ムラムラしたりじゃないの?
Yeah.
うん
Because I had a boyfriend?
彼氏いたから?
I want you to lick it.
舐めてほしいです
That's also true though.
それもあるけど
Sticks are also growing.
棒も生えてる
Just a little bit, like.
ちょっとね、みたいな
Do you care?
気にする?
Socially.
社会的に